Finding Aid for the Delbert Mann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Productions
  - Productions Directed by Others
    - Othello, 1953; Walter’ Matthau, Torin Thatcher (Box 99)
    - Our Town, 1940; Sam Tarpley, Frances Carter, Delbert Mann (Box 99)
    - Our Town, 1955; Eva Marie Saint, Paul Newman (Box 99)
    - The Outsider, 1960 (3), Tony Curtis Recreation of Iwo Jima Flag Raising Iwo Jima Monument, Washington, D.C., Joe LaShelle, Delbert Mann, Marshall Green (Box 99)
    - The Petrified Forest, 1955 (3), Jack Klugman, Morris Buchanan, Richard Jaeckel, Humphrey Bogart Lauren Bacall, Henry Fonda Joseph Sweeney, Richard Gaines, Henry Fonda, Natalie Schaefer, Humphrey Bogart (Box 99)
    - The Pink Jungle, 1967 (3), James Garner Location, Mojave Desert Princess Grace of Monaco and her two children, Princess Caroline and Prince Albert (Box 99)
    - The Plot to Kill Stalin, 1959; Eli Wallach, Melvyn Douglas (Box 99)
    - Quick, Before It Melts, 1963 (2), Delbert Mann, Penguin (“Milton Fox”), Robert Morse, George Maharis George Maharis, Robert Morse (Box 99)
    - A Quiet Place, 1955; Delbert Mann, Leora Dana, Tyrone Power, Julian Claman (Box 99)
    - The Rich Boy, 1952; Gene Lyons, Grace Kelly (Box 99)
    - Separate Tables, 1958 (3), Burt Lancaster, Delbert Mann, Rita Hayworth David Niven, Wendy Hiller Deborah Kerr, Rita Hayworth, Hilda Plowright, Burt Lancaster, Gladys Cooper, Wendy Hiller, David Niven, Rod Taylor, Audrey Dalton, Felix Aylmer (Box 99)
    - Television Academy of Arts & Sciences Tribute to Delbert Mann, 1988; Richard Dysart, Ernest Borgnine, Eva Marie Saint, Delbert Mann, Richard Thomas, Lee Remick, Unidentified, Jackie Cooper, Michael Gross, Betsy Palmer (Box 99)
    - That Touch of Mink, 1962 (3), Cary Grant, Doris Day Roger Maris, Doris Day, Mickey Mantle, Cary Grant, Yogi Berra Doris Day, Cary Grant (Box 99)
    - Tovarich, 1962 (3), John Emery, Vivien Leigh, Jean Pierre Aumont, Delbert Mann Jean Pierre Aumont, Vivien Leigh, Byron Mitchell First Rehearsal (Box 99)
    - The Tunnel, 1959; The Battle of the Crater (1864) (Box 99)
    - Twelfth Night, 1940; Delbert Mann, Jane Allen, Hamilton Douglas (Box 99)
    - Vincent Van Gogh, 1950 (2), Everett Sloan (Box 99)
    - What Makes Sammy Run?, 1959; David Opatoshu, Larry Blyden, Sidney Blackmer, Dina Merrill (Box 99)
    - Yellow Jack, 1955; Eva Marie Saint, Rod Steiger (Box 99)
    - VIDEOTAPES AND AUDIOTAPES (Box 100)
    - Productions, The Marriages (Philco Playhouse) The Medea Cup (Goodyear Playhouse) Othello (Masterpiece Theatre, incomplete) Recluse (Goodyear Playhouse) Search (Goodyear Playhouse) Segment (Philco Playhouse) The Symbol (Philco Playhouse) Wish on the Moon (Goodyear Playhouse) Without Fear or Favor (Philco Playhouse) (Box 100)
    - Miscellaneous, Holiday Song, directed by Gordon Duff (Philco Playhouse) George Schaefer Interview with Lynn Fontaine, 1980 Miller & Company, Interview, 21 November 1982 Interview with Susan Armistead, WPLN Radio, Nashville, April 1989 (Box 100)
    - VIDEOTAPES AND AUDIOTAPES (Box 101)
    - Productions, The Marriages (Philco Playhouse) The Medea Cup (Goodyear Playhouse) Othello (Masterpiece Theatre, incomplete) Recluse (Goodyear Playhouse) Search (Goodyear Playhouse) Segment (Philco Playhouse) The Symbol (Philco Playhouse) Wish on the Moon (Goodyear Playhouse) Without Fear or Favor (Philco Playhouse) (Box 101)
    - Miscellaneous, Holiday Song, directed by Gordon Duff (Philco Playhouse) George Schaefer Interview with Lynn Fontaine, 1980 Miller & Company, Interview, 21 November 1982 Interview with Susan Armistead, WPLN Radio, Nashville, April 1989 (Box 101)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 102)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 103)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 104)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 105)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 106)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 107)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 108)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 109)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 110)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 111)
    - SCRAPBOOKS, Volume I, 1949-1953 Volume II, 1955 Volume III, 1955 Volume IV, 1956 Volume V, 1956-1957 Volume VI, 1957-1958 Volume VII, 1959 Volume VIII, 1958-1959 Volume IX, 1960 Volume X, 1961 Volume XI, 1963 Volume XII, 1963-1964 Volume XIII, 1965 Volume XIV, 1966-1968 Volume XV, 1968-1969 Volume XVI, 1970-1972 Volume XVII, 1973-1975 Volume XVIII, 1974 Volume XIX, 1975-1977 Volume XX, 1977-1979 Volume XXI, 1979-1981 Volume XXII, 1981-1983 Volume XXIII, 1982 Volume XXIV, 1983-1984 Volume XXV, 1983-1986 Volume XXVI, 1986-1988 (Box 112)
    - OVERSIZE MATERIALS (Box 113)
    - WRITINGS –, “A Remembrance of Pappy: Fred Coe, 1914-1979” Program, Tennessee Performing Arts Center, 8 September 1980 (Box 113)
    - AUDIOTAPES –, The Red Mill – Music She Waits – Music (Box 113)
    - OVERSIZE MATERIALS, Fred Coe, 10th Anniverary in Television, Variety, May 23, 1956 April Morning – Set Designs, Sketches Breaking Up – Set Design The Dark at the Top of the Stairs – Exterior Farm Drawing, Schedule David Copperfield – Scene and Actor Breakdown Fitzwilly – Set Designs, Sketches, Schedules The Gift of Love – Set Designs A Girl Named Sooner – Set Designs The Glass Menagerie – Set Designs Heidi – Set Designs The Huntress – Set Design Incident in Baltimore – Schedules Jane Eyre – Schedules Kidnapped – Schedule, Sketches Lover, Come Back – Schedules, Sketches Love’s Dark Ride – Set Design The Memoirs of Abraham Lincoln – Set Design Middle of the Night, 1959 – Set Design Night Crossing – Schedules, Story Boards (Sketches), Location Information Our Town – Program, Emmy Awards The Pink Jungle – Location Photographs Separate Tables – Sketches She Waits – Schedules God’s Guerillas – set design Tom and Joann – Set Designs (Box 114)
    - OVERSIZE MATERIALS (Map and Print File) (Box 114)
    - Set Designs (unless otherwise noted), All the Way Home – 4 items April Morning – 22 items Bachelor Party, 1953 – 1 item Bachelor Party, 1957 – Set Sketches, 4 items Ben Franklin, American – 16 items Birch Interval, Location Maps – 2 items Bronte – 2 items Darkness at Noon – 1 item David Copperfield – 29 items The Day Lincoln Was Shot – 2 items A Death in California – Poster, Greek Language, 1 item Ernie Barger Is 50 – 1 item The First Woman President – 11 items Fitzwilly – 14 items A Girl Named Sooner – 1 item The Haven – 1 item Ironclads – 12 items Jane Eyre – 49 items Joie (Love Story) – 4 items Kidnapped – 35 items The Legendary curse of the Hope Diamond – 32 items Love’s Dark Ride – 4 items The Man Without a Country – 14 items Marty, 1953 – 1 item The Medea Cup – 1 item The Member of the Wedding – 13 items Night Crossing – 24 items No Place to Run – 10 items Operation Airlift – 1 item Othello – 3 items Our Town – 2 items Petrified Forest, 1955 – 2 items The Pink Jungle – 26 items The Plot to Kill Stalin – 2 items The Rich Boy – 1 item Roots II – 4 items Saturday Adoption – 2 items Say It Ain’t So, Joe – 5 items Speaking of Murder – 3 items Stage 10, Live: The Petrified Forest – 8 items Tell Me My Name – 29 items Thou Shalt Not Commit Adultery – 2 items To Find My Son – 1 item Tom and Joann – 13 items Wings Over Barriers – 1 item Wuthering Heights (1959) – 3 items Yellow Jack – 1 item Your Place or Mine – 6 items Zelda – 4 items (Box 114)